infobeasiswa.net 2014-06-29

# Privacy Policy - Info Beasiswa

**InfoBeasiswa.net Privacy Statement**

What follows is the Privacy Statement for all Scholarship websites (a.k.a. blogs) including all the websites run under the InfoBeasiswa.net domain.

Please read this statement regarding our blogs. If you have questions please ask us via our contact form.

**Email Addresses**

You may choose to add your email address to our contact list via the forms on our websites. We agree that we will never share you email with any third party and that we will remove your email at your request. We donâ€™t currently send advertising via email, but in the future our email may contain advertisements and we may send dedicated email messages from our advertisers without revealing your email addresses to them. If you have any problem removing your email address please contact us via our contact form.

**Ownership of Information**

InfoBeasiswa.net is the sole owner of any information collected on our websites.

**Comments/Message Boards**

Most InfoBeasiswa.net websites contain comment sections (a.k.a. message boards). We do not actively monitor these comments and the information on them is for entertainment purposes only. If we are alerted to something we deem inappropriate in any way, we may delete it at our discretion. We use email validation on most of our message boards in order to reduce â€œcomment spam.â€ These email addresses will not be shared with any third party.

**Cookies**

Currently we assign cookies to our readers in order to save their preferences. This data is not shared with any third party. Accessing our websites is not dependent on accepting cookies and all major browsers allow you to disable cookies if you wish.

**Third Party Cookies**

Many of our advertisers use cookies in order to determine the number of times you have seen an advertisement. This is done to limit the number times you are shown the same advertisement. InfoBeasiswa.net does not have access to this data.

**Updated March 27, 2009**

> We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

**Traffic Reports**

Our industry-standard traffic reporting records IP addresses, Internet service provider information, referrer strings, browser types and the date and time pages are loaded. We use this information in the aggregate only to provide traffic statistics to advertisers and to figure out which features and editorials are most popular.

**Legal proceedings**

We will make every effort to preserve user privacy but InfoBeasiswa.net may need to disclose information when required by law.

**Business Transitions**

If InfoBeasiswa.net is acquired by or merges with another firm, the assets of our websites, including personal information, will likely be transferred to the new firm.

**Links**

InfoBeasiswa.net websites frequently link to other websites. We are not responsible for the content or business practices of these websites. When you leave our websites we encourage you to read the destination siteâ€™s privacy policy. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by InfoBeasiswa.net

**Notification of Changes**

When InfoBeasiswa.net makes changes to this privacy policy we will post those changes here.

**Contact Information**

If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy, please[ contact us](http://www.infobeasiswa.net/contact/).
